<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dice Roller</string>
    <string name="txt_roll">roll</string>
    <string name="txt_shital">shital</string>
    <string name="txt_star">Star</string>
    <string name="about_me"> I am shital.\n
        We are five members in my family including me. \n
        I am native to —— (City Name), and open to relocate to ________ (city name as mentioned in the job description). Currently, I am pursuing B.A. in Economics at the ___________ (University Name), and I will be entering into final year of my graduation studies in the next couple of months. Ever since, I started studying Economics in my school days.
        \n \nI realized, I enjoy analyzing things connected to the society, and the Mother Nature. Since my childhood days, I have witnessed my family focusing upon correct utilization of house hold items, and guiding us towards understanding the whites, and blacks of the possible outcomes. I believe, this somehow further boosted my interest towards Economics as a career option.

For me Economics is all about making right decisions at the right time, and studying the possible outcomes.
I have an analytical approach towards things I do. I believe, that helps me to understand a wide range of issues from what determines the price, causes, and consequences.
I believe, economics is having an excellent graduate prospects. \n\nEconomics is truly all around us. Studying the subject gives me a generalist understanding of the world we live in and its inner workings.
The case-based learning emphasis on economics degrees makes it really easy to see how the theory has real-life applications, particularly when considering the recent volatility of global markets.</string>
    <string name="txt_shital_rahane">Shital Rahane</string>
    <string name="enter_nick_name">What is your nick name?</string>
    <string name="done">done!</string>
    <string name="box_one">Box One</string>
    <string name="box_two">Box Two</string>
    <string name="box_three">Box Three</string>
    <string name="box_four">Box Four</string>
    <string name="box_five">Box Five</string>
    <string name="btn_red">Red</string>
    <string name="btn_green">Green</string>
    <string name="btn_yellow">Yellow</string>
</resources>